The call of the wild. The thrill of adventure. The mistake of a lifetime.
Without a Paddle is a comedy, action, adventure film directed by Steven Brill.
Three friends, whose lives have been drifting apart, reunite
for the funeral of a fourth childhood friend.
When looking through their childhood belongings, they discover a trunk which
contained details on a quest their friend was attempting.
It revealed that he was hot on the trail of the $200,000
that went missing with airplane hijacker D.B.
Cooper in 1971.
They decide to continue his journey, but do not
understand the dangers they will soon encounter.
Dan Mott, played by Seth Green.
Jerry Conlaine, played by Matthew Lillard.
Tom Marshall, played by Dax Shepard.
Elwood, played by Ethan Suplee.
Dennis, played by Abraham Benrubi.
Billy Newwood, played by Antony Starr.
Without a Paddle is a 2004 American adventure comedy film directed by Steven Brill, written by Jay
Leggett and Mitch Rouse, and based on a story by Harris Goldberg, Tom Nursall, and Fred Wolf.
The film stars Seth Green, Matthew Lillard, Dax Shepard, Ethan Suplee, Abraham Benrubi, Rachel
Blanchard, Christina Moore, Bonnie Somerville, Ray Baker, and Burt Reynolds.
It tells the story of three reunited childhood friends going on a trip up a remote
river in order to search for the loot of long-lost airplane hijacker D.
Without a Paddle was released by Paramount Pictures on August 20, 2004.
The film received mostly negative reviews from critics and
grossed $73 million against a $19 million budget.
A direct-to-video sequel, entitled Without a Paddle:
Nature's Calling, was released in January 2009.
The film explores themes of friendship, loss of loved
one, camping, wilderness, treasure hunt.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.